{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"71.5/6.5",
			"answer":"71.5/6.5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.312/0.26",
			"answer":"0.312/0.26",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2.43/0.027",
			"answer":"2.43/0.027",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.212/0.53",
			"answer":"0.212/0.53",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"56.4/9.4",
			"answer":"56.4/9.4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"52.8/0.012",
			"answer":"52.8/0.012",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1.98/1.8",
			"answer":"1.98/1.8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.918/0.09",
			"answer":"0.918/0.09",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1.46/7.3",
			"answer":"1.46/7.3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"60.4/10",
			"answer":"60.4/10",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}

	]
}